Milch Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Miscellaneous, 1916-1970, undated, Series 6:
  - Shipping receipts (bound), prepaid, cont., 1955-1965 (Reel 4465)
Feb. 16-March 7, 1953 Recent Watercolors by Jerri Ricci
April 6-25, 1953 Recent Watercolors by John Whorf
May 18-29, 1953 Richard Whorf
May 18-29, 1953 Paintings by New York Artists, 21st Exhibition of the Arthur Schwieder Group
June, 1953 Paintings and Watercolors by 19th and 20th Century American Artists
Oct., 1953 Paintings and Watercolors by American Artists
Oct. 26-Nov. 14, 1953 Recent Paintings by David Burr Moreing
Nov. 17-Dec. 5, 1953 Ogden W. Pleissner Recent Paintings
Dec. 7-30, 1953 Recent Landscapes by Sidney Laufman
Jan. 4-23, 1954 Paintings of New York's "Little Italy" by Frank di Gioia
Jan. 25-Feb. 13, 1954 Round the World by Watercolor with Eliot O'Hara, N.A.
Feb. 15-March 6, 1954 Hobson Pittman
March 8-27, 1954 Jay Robinson: Kentucky, Part II
April 5-24, 1954 John Whorf Watercolors
May 17-28, 1954 Paintings by New York Artists, 22nd Exhibition of the Arthur Schwieder Group
Oct. 25-Nov. 13, 1954 Recent Watercolors by James Vance
Nov. 15-Dec. 4, 1954 Stephen Etnier Recent Paintings
Dec. 6-24, 1954 Recent Paintings by Thomas Blagden
Jan. 3-22, 1955 Recent Paintings by Jacques Zucker
Jan. 24-Feb. 12, 1955 Recent Watercolors by Jerri Ricci
Feb. 14-March 5, 1955 Paintings of Spain and Her People by Maurice Fromkes
April 25-May 14, 1955 Gluckmann Recent Paintings
May 16-27, 1955 Paintings by New York Artists, 23rd Exhibition of the Arthur Schwieder Group
Oct. 24-Nov. 12, 1955 Paintings and Gouaches by John Taylor
Nov. 14-Dec. 3, 1955 Paintings and Panels by Jay Robinson of West and Central Africa
Dec. 5-30, 1955 Childe Hassam and American Impressionism
Jan., 1956 Recent Paintings by a Group of American Artists
Feb. 6-25, 1956 F. Douglas Greenbowe Watercolors
March, 1956 Group Exhibition
April 9-28, 1956 John Whorf Watercolors
May, 1956 Paintings by a Group of 18 American Artists
May 7-19, 1956 Paintings by New York Artists, 24th Exhibition of the Arthur Schwieder Group
Nov. 5-24, 1956 Stephen Etnier Recent Paintings
Nov. 27-Dec. 15, 1956 Ogden M. Pleissner Recent Paintings
Dec. 1-Jan. 19, 1957 Jay Robinson Paintings in Fired Enamel on Copper
Feb. 11-March 2, 1957 Recent Paintings by Thomas Blagden
March 4-23, 1957 Adolph Dehn
April 15-May 4, 1957 John Whorf Watercolors
Oct. 28-Nov. 16, 1957 Recent Still Life Paintings by Aaron Bohrod
Jan. 13-Feb. 8, 1958 Recent Paintings by a Group of Contemporary Americans
Feb. 10-March 8, 1958 Long Island Paintings by Childe Hassam
March 10-29, 1958 Paintings by Louis Di Valentin
March 31-April 19, 1958 Recent Paintings by Sidney Laufman
April 21-May 10, 1958 John Whorf Watercolors
May, 1958 Americans: 1865-1925
June, 1958 Exhibit to Benefit Friends of the Whitney Museum
June 3-27, 1958 American Paintings and Sculpture
Oct. 6-25, 1958 Recent Paintings by David Shapiro
Oct. 27-Nov. 15, 1958 Stephen Etnier Recent Paintings
Nov. 17-Dec. 6, 1958 Paul Sample Recent Paintings
Dec. 8-24, 1958 Recent Drawings and Watercolors of France, Italy, Spain, and North Africa by Frank di Gioia
Jan. 19-Feb. 7, 1959 Marion Greenwood Paintings
March 2-21, 1959 Leon Kroll Paintings and Drawings
March 23-April 18, 1959 Elmer L. Mac Rae Forgotten Artist of the 1913 Armory Show
May 4-23, 1959 Philip Visson
Oct., 1959 Paintings by American Artists
Oct. 26-Nov. 14, 1959 Recent Painting by Aaron Bohrod
Nov. 17-Dec. 5, 1959 Ogden M. Pleissner Recent Paintings
Dec. 7-30, 1959 Recent Oils and Watercolors by Thomas Blagden
Jan. 18-Feb. 6, 1960 Elmer L. Mac Rae, Re-Discovered Artist of the 1913 Armory Show and a Founder of "The Pastellists"
through Jan. 15, 1960 Paintings by American Artists
March 14-April 2, 1960 Xavier Gonzalez Recent Paintings
April 4-23, 1960 Paintings by Louis Bosa
April 25-May 14, 1960 Grigory Gluckmann
May-June, 1960 Group of Contemporary Armerican Artists
Oct. 10-29, 1960 Adolf Dehn Caseins and Watercolors
Oct. 31-Nov. 19, 1960 Stephen Etnier
Dec., 1960 Paintings for the Home
Jan., 1961 Group Exhibition, 19th and 20th Century Americans
Jan. 30-Feb. 18, 1961 Recent Watercolors by Jerri Ricci
Feb. 20-March 11, 1961 Frank di Gioia Recent Paintings
March 20-April 8, 1961 David Fredenthal Memorial Exhibition
April 10-29, 1961 Allen Tucker
May, 1961 Contemporary American Artists
June-July, 1961 19th & 20th Century American Artists
Oct. 10-28, 1961 David Shapiro Recent Paintings
Oct. 31-Nov. 18, 1961 Aaron Bohrod
Nov. 21-Dec. 9, 1961 Thomas Fransioli
Feb. 6-24, 1962 Retrospective Exhibition, Maurice Sterne
March 6-24, 1962 Three Watercolorists: Childe Hassam, John Whorf, and David Fredenthal
April 3-21, 1962 Thomas Blagden
April 24-May 12, 1962 Grigory Gluckmann
Summer, 1962 Gallery Group of Contemporary Americans
Sept., 1962 19th & 20th Century American Artists
Oct., 1962 Gallery Group of Contemporary Americans
Oct. 30-Nov. 17, 1962 Stephen Etnier
Nov. 21-Dec. 8, 1962 Pleissner Recent Paintings
Dec., 1962 Group Exhibition
Jan. 22-Feb. 9, 1963 Paul Sample Recent Paintings
Feb. 11-March 2, 1963 Group of Contemporary Americans
March 5-23, 1963 Gouaches by John Taylor
March 26-April 13, 1963 Fletcher Martin Recent Paintings
April-May, 1963 Gallery Group-Contemporary Americans
Oct. 8-26, 1963 David Shapiro Recent Work
Oct. 30-Nov. 16, 1963 Xavier Gonzalez Recent Watercolors
Nov. 19-Dec. 7, 1963 New Paintings by Aaron Bohrod
April, 1964 Watercolors and Pastels
April 21-May 9, 1964 Grigory Gluckmann
May 13-29, 1964 Frank di Gioia Recent Paintings
Oct., 1964 Group Exhibition
Nov. 3-21, 1964 Stephen Etnier
Nov. 24-Dec. 12, 1964 Thomas Blagden
Jan., 1965 Comtemporary American Artists
Feb. 2-14, 1965 Figure Paintings by Murray Bewley
Feb. 2-14, 1965 Exhibition by George Biddle
Feb. 11-23, 1965 Paintings and Drawings by Max Bohm
Feb. 14-26, 1965 Paintings by Arthur C. Goodwin
Feb. 16-28, 1965 Water Colors by Matilda Browne
Feb. 16-March 6, 1965 Water Colors by Adolf Dehn
March, 1965 19th and 20th Century American Artists
March 1-13, 1965 Bruce Crane, N.A.
March 6-25, 1965 Pastels of the Cascapedia River, Canada, by Arthur C. Goodwin
March 26-April 7, 1965 Paintings by Howard Russell Butler, N.A.
March 23-April 10, 1965 Paintings by Dan Lutz
March 28-April 16, 1965 Paintings by Henry Golden Dearth
April 2-21, 1965 Landscape Paintings by Bruce Crane, N.A.
April 13-May 1, 1965 Paintings by Louis Bosa
April 16-28, 1965 Water Colors and Etchings by Adolphe W. Blondheim
May, 1965 Gallery Contemporaries
Oct. 25-Nov. 13, 1965 Recent Landscapes by John F. Carlson, N.A.
Oct. 26-Nov. 13, 1965 Twenty-Four New Paintings by Aaron Bohrod, Artist in Residence, University of Wisconsin
Nov. 2-14, 1965 Paintings by Ann Crane
Nov. 5-17, 1965 Memorial Exhibition of Paintings of Venice by Wm. Gedney Bunce, N.A.
Nov. 7-19, 1965 Paintings and Sculpture by Matilda Browne
Nov. 16-Dec. 4, 1965 Electra Bostwick
Dec. 7-30, 1965 Recent Drawings and Watercolors of European Countries and North Africa by Frank di Gioia
Jan. 11-29, 1966 Georges Schreiber Watercolors: 1963-1965
Jan.-Feb., 1966 19th and 20th Century American Artists
Feb.-March, 1966 Group Exhibition
June, 1966 Group Exhibition
Oct. 11-29, 1966 Thomas Blagden
Nov. 1-19, 1966 Stephen Etnier
Nov. 22-Dec. 10, 1966 Pleissner
Jan. 24-Feb. 11, 1967 Xavier Gonzalez
April, 1967 Group Exhibition
April 18-May 6, 1967 Grigory Gluckmann
July, 1967 Group Exhibition
undated Etchings and Color-Etchings
undated Etchings of China and Cambodia by Lucille Douglass
undated Thomas Jefferson Bust in Bronze by Robert Aitken, N.A.
undated Paintings by Ossip L. Linde
undated Etchings by William Meyerowitz
undated Recent Screens and Panels by Roy Mac Nicol
undated Summer Exhibition of Paintings and Watercolors by 19th and 20th Century American Artists
undated Paintings by Clement
undated Important Works in Paintings and Sculpture by Leading American Artists
Jan. 3-14, undated Armin Hansen
Jan. 8-27, undated* Recent Etchings by William Meyerowitz
Jan. 8-31, undated Group of American Figure Paintings, 19th and 20th Century
Jan. 9-21, undated Paintings by Katherine Langhorne Adams
Jan. 16-28, undated Paintings by Dewitt Parshall, N.A., and Douglass Parshall, N.A.
Jan. 23-Feb. 11, undated Paintings by Bruce Crane, Elliott Daingerfield, Granville Smith, and F. Ballard Williams
Jan. 27-Feb. 11, undated Willam de Leftwick Dodge
Jan. 28-Feb. 16, undated Paintings by Gari Melchers
Jan. 29-Feb. 10, undated Paintings of the California Coast by Armin Hansen
Jan. 30-Feb. 11, undated Sigrud Skou
Feb. 13-25, undated Water Colors by Alice Judson
Feb. 13-25, undated Paintings by Guy Wiggins, N.A.
Feb. 13-March 11, undated Paintings by H.T. Keasbey
Feb. 15-March 5, undated Frederic James
Feb. 17-March 1, undated Silver Point Drawings by Thelma E. Wood
Feb. 18-March 6, undated Landcapes, Nature Moods Expressed in Terms of Light by Julie Mathilde Morrow
Feb. 18-March 8, undated Paintings of Venice, Rome and French Landscape, also Pastel Drawings of the Battle Sectors of the 26th Division, A.E.F. by J. Alden Twachtman
Feb. 27-March 10, undated Portrait Busts and Drawings by Alexander Portnoff
March 5-17, undated* Pastels of the Hudson River by Arthur C. Goodwin
March 7-16, undated Paintings of Africa and Spain by Lillian Genth
March 7-26, undated Sigurd Skou
March 8-20, undated Paintings by Sigurd Skou
March 10-22, undated MacDowell Club of New York City Annual Exhibition of Paintings
March 22-April 10, undated Paintings of the Cathedrals of France by Pieter Van Veen
March 26-April 12, undated Paintings by E. Martin Hennings
March 26-April 14, undated Recent Etchings by Elias M. Grossman
March 28-April 16, undated Martha Walter Water Colors of Spain and North Africa
April 5-17, undated Paintings by Ernest L. Blumenschein, Victor Huggins, Walter Ufer
April 7-19, undated Figure Paintings by Louis Ritman
April 12-23, undated Portraits and Figure Paintings by Edith Catlin Phelps
April 12-24, undated Paintings of American Gardens by Abbott Graves
April 16-28, undated Portrait Drawings in Pastel by Jessie Voss Lewis (Mrs. H.L. Daingerfield Lewis)
April 19-May 1, undated Paintings by Valentino Molina
April 21-May 3, undated Paintings of Tahiti and California by William Ritschel, N.A.
April 21-May 3, undated Leonard Lopp, Glacier Park Artist
April 22-May 15, undated Sculpture for House, Garden & Grounds by Leading American Artists, and Pottery by Clara L. Poillon
April 24-May 5, undated Paintings by Thalia Millett
April 26-May 15, undated Dan Lutz, Mighican Summer and Mexican Sojourn
April 26-May 15, undated William H. Singer
April 27-May 16, undated Recent Paintings by Gluckmann
May 3-28, undated Exhibition of Sculpture for Garden and Grounds by Leading Sculptors
May 5-17, undated Recent American Sculpture in Bronze, Wood and Terra Cotta for the Town and Country House, Grounds and Garden
Oct. 11-23, undated Paintings by Anna Heyward Taylor
Oct. 25-Nov. 13, undated Water Colors by Alice Judson
Oct. 27-Nov. 15, undated Paintings and Etchings by William Auerbach-Levy
Oct. 30-Nov. 11, undated* Connecticut Landscape Paintings by Robert Nisbet, A.N.A.
Oct. 31-Nov. 12, undated Paintings of China and Tibet by Alice Job
Oct. 31-Nov. 14, undated Drawings by James Wilkie
Nov. 5-17, undated Paintings of Venice
Nov. 15-27, undated* Water Colors by Childe Hassam
Nov. 16-Dec. 5, undated Recent Etchings by Alfred Hutty
Nov. 16-Dec. 5, undated Paintings by W. Elmer Schofield
Nov. 17-29, undated Paintings and Etchings by Power O'Malley
Nov. 18-30, undated Recent Work in Water Color and Etching by Louis Wolchonok
Nov. 19-Dec. 1, undated Winter Landscapes in Water Color by Walter Launt Palmer, N.A.
Nov. 19-Dec. 1, undated Painter Friends, Robert H. Nisbet, Guy C, Wiggins, Edward C. Volkert, Wilson Irvine, George M. Bruestle, and Carl J. Nordell
Nov. 23-, undated Landscapes by Ault, Brook, Coleman, Karfiol, Ritman, Speight, Sterne, and Weber
Nov. 23-Dec. 6, undated Portraits of America's Most Distinguished Women by Leon Gordon
Nov. 24-Dec. 3, undated Sculpture by Gleb Derujinsky
Nov. 26-Dec., undated Exhibition of Recent Vermont Landscapes by Edward Bruce
Nov. 26-Dec. 5, undated Alfred Hutty
Nov. 27-Dec. 9, undated Paintings by Sigure Schou
Dec. 1-27, undated Works Painted in Spain by Maurice Fromkes
Dec. 1-25, undated Annual Holiday Exhibition of Selected Paintings of Limited Size
Dec. 3-29, undated Recent Paintings, Water Colors, and Etchings by Hilde Hassam, N.A., of the American Academy of Arts and Letters
Dec. 6-30, undated Selected Paintings for the Home by American Artists
Dec. 14-Jan. 2, undated Recent Paintings by George Shillard
Dec. 20-Jan. 8, undated Selected Small Paintings for the Home
Dec. 27-Jan. 12, undated Helen K. McCarthy Memorial Exhibition
Dec. 30-Jan. 18, undated Paintings by Stewart McDermot
Dec. 31-Jan. 12, undated Second Annual Exhibition in Pure Water Color by The Aquarellists